Guide to the Overbrook Press Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
Overbrook Press Records,
1929-1978
[Bulk: 1935-1961]
Overbrook Press.
6.3 linear feet ( 15 document boxes)
Columbia University. Rare Book and Manuscript Library New York, NY. 10027
MS#0959
4079185
This collection documents the operation of Overbrook Press, a private American press once located in Stamford, Connecticut, from its founding by Frank Altschul in 1934 until it ceased operation in 1969.
Historical Note
The Overbrook Press was founded in 1934 in Stamford, Connecticut, by Frank Altschul, an investment banker and civic leader with a lifelong interest in book arts and printing. Altschul initially pursued printing as a hobby, experimenting with a small press in his New York apartment. In 1934, he was approached by designer Margaret B. Evans, who had been working for Ashlar Press. Ashlar was closing, and Evans hoped Altschul would continue its work.
Altschul set up the press in converted outbuildings on his Stamford farm and hired Evans as designer and compositor and John MacNamara as pressman. The Overbrook Press went on to print an eclectic variety of books and pamphlets, as well as ephemera such as awards and certificates. Evens placed great emphasis on technical expertise and craftsmanship, and even smaller pieces - political pamphlets such as Towards a More Creative Policy and short books on chess problems - were handled with surprising care.
Altschul set up the press in converted outbuildings on his Stamford farm and hired Evans as designer and compositor and John MacNamara as pressman. The Overbrook Press went on to print an eclectic variety of books and pamphlets, as well as ephemera such as awards and certificates. Evens placed great emphasis on technical expertise and craftsmanship, and even smaller pieces - political pamphlets such as "Toward a More Creative Policy" and short books on chess problems - were handled with unusual care.
Overbrook volumes were also known for fine illustrations. In the 1930s, the Overbrook Press published an edition of Robert Louis Stevenson's travelogue An Inland Voyage, which featured illustrations by French artist Jean Hugo. Hugo was commissioned to follow Stevenson's path through Belgium and France and produce gouaches of scenes along the route. The press worked with many other artists, including Valenti Angelo, Anna Simons, and Bruce Rogers, but is most closely associated with T.M. Cleland, who illustrated a number of Overbrook volumes. His most ambitious project was an edition of Prevost's Manon Lescaut, for which he created elaborate silk-screened illustrations. The volume, which was published in 1958 after six years of work, is considered one of the highest quality private press books of the time.
The Overbrook Press operated for nearly thirty years, closing its doors in 1969.
Scope and Content
This collection contains materials relating to approximately 150 of the books, pamphlets, and broadsides printed by the Overbrook Press from its founding in 1934 until its last year of activity, 1969. It also includes a small amount of earlier records relating to the Helealt Corporation, the fiscal parent of Overbrook Press. Approximately two-thirds of the collection consists of business correspondence between Altschul, authors, and agents. The collection also contains a great deal of correspondence between Frank Altschul and noted artists and book designers such as Valenti Angelo, W.A. Dwiggins, Jean Hugo, Rudoph Ruzicka, Daniel B. Updike, Thomas M. Cleland, and Elmer Adler. Correspondence on a particular book or pamphlet is sometimes accompanied by proofs, drafts, or an example of the final product. The collection also contains memoranda, manuscripts, and financial records. Particularly noteworthy are the files relating to the publication of Manon Lescaut(1958), Robert Louis Stevenson's Inland Voyage (1938), and Herbert Cahoon's 1963 Overbrook Press Bibliography.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into two series:
Series I: Correspondence, 1933-1978
Subseries I.1: Alphabetical Correspondence, 1934-1976
Subseries I.2: Author-Title Files, 1933-1969
Subseries I.3: General Correspondence, 1934-1978
Series II: General, 1929-1977
Subjects
Helealt Corporation.; Overbrook Press.; Altschul, Frank, 1887-1981.; Angelo, Valenti, 1897-1982.; Dwiggins, W. A. (William Addison), 1880-1956.; Hugo, Jean, 1894-1984.; Ruzicka, Rudolph, 1883-1978.; Updike, Daniel Berkeley, 1860-1941.; Cleland, T. M. (Thomas Maitland), 1880-1964.; Adler, Elmer, 1884-1962.; Dulles, John Foster, 1888-1959.; Frankfurter, Felix, 1882-1965.; Gunther, John, 1901-1970.; Luce, Clare Boothe, 1903-1987.; MacLeish, Archibald, 1892-1982.; Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich), 1908-1979.; Evans, Margaret B.; Stevenson, Robert Louis, 1850-1894.; Cahoon, Herbert, 1918-2000.; Artists.; Book design.; Illustration of books.; Layout (printing).; Presswork (printing).; Typography; Publishers and publishing--Connecticut--Stamford.; Literature publishing.; Scholarly publishing.; Civic leaders--Connecticut--Stamford.; Philanthropists.; Book collectors.
Access Restrictions
This collection is located off-site. You will need to request this material at least twenty-four (24) hours in advance to use the collection in the Rare Book and Manuscript Library reading room.
This collection has no restrictions.
Acquisition
1980 M-80 Altschul, Frank Gift
Related Material
Herbert H. Lehman Papers, 1858-1963 Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Columbia University
Frank Altschul Papers, 1884-1986 Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Columbia University
Online finding aid available.
- Series I: Correspondence, 1933-1978
  This series contains correspondence of three types; alphabetical correspondence arranged by surname, author-title files containing correspondence relating to specific works, and general chronological correspondence.
  - Subseries I.1: Alphabetical Correspondence, 1934-1976
    This subseries contains letters to Altschul from artists, actors, politicians, and other individuals outside the publishing field. Most are brief letters of thanks in response to the complementary books Altschul often sent to notable figures. Files have been arranged alphabetically by correspondent name.
    - Acheson, Dean--Macmahon, Arthur, (96 Folders) (Box 1)
    - Malik, Charles--Wood, Rose Mary, (57 Folders) (Box 2)
  - Subseries I.2: Author-Title Files, 1933-1969
    Files in this subseries hold correspondence between Altschul and authors, editors, illustrators, and others regarding the design and publication of books, broadsides, and pamphlets. Many also contain drafts, proofs, or final copies of broadsides and pamphlets. In general, files are arranged alphabetically by author and contain correspondence related to the publishing of a single work, though in some cases they may cover several works by the same author. It is unclear whether this arrangement is original or was imposed at a later date.
    - Acheson, Dean--"Fifty Years After," 1961 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Adams, Frederick B. Jr.--Radical Literature in America, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - "Address to the People by Certain Members of the Senate," 1938 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Adler, Elmer--Menu for a Dinner Honoring Adler, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Aldington, Richard--A Dream in the Luxemburg, 1935 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Aldrich, Amy--"Fifty Years Ago," 1959 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Allen, Edgar W. and Eric M. Hassenberg--To Alain White: A Tribute, 1945 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Altschul, Charles--"The Influence of England," 1954 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - American Political Science Association--Award Scrolls, 1948-1953 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Annalita--"Be Careful," 1968 (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Armstrong, Hamilton Fish--"The Task and Price of World Leadership," 1947 (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Baerwald, Emil, 1869-1948--Quotations from his Funeral Service, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Ballantine, Arthur A.--Poems, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Baruch, Bernard M.--"Freedom for Man: A World Safe for Mankind: An Address," Introduction by August Hekscher, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Benton, William--"Brien McMahon: A Tribute," 1952 (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Bingham, June--Do Cows have Neuroses? 1948 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Borg, Madelaine, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Breton, Nicholas and Bruce Rogers (Illustrator)--Twelve Months, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Brewster, Kingman--Style, Pluck and Integrity, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Buschke, Albrecht, Richard Cheney and Alan White--The Two-Move Chess Problem in the Soviet Union, 1923-1943, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Cahoon, Herbert, Compiler--The Overbrook Press Bibliography, 1963, (2 Folders) (Box 3, Folder 6 to 7)
    - California, State Senate Concurrent Resolution No. 12, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Chiang May Ling Soong--Addresses, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Churchill, Winston Spencer--An Address by Winston S. Churchill, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Cleland, Thomas Maitland--"Progress" in the Graphic Arts, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Clemens, Samuel L.--Three Sketches, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Cohn, Alfred E. et al--A Memorandum on the Need for a New Journal on higher Education in the United States, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Cohn, David L.--America to England, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Conant, James B.--The Defense of Freedom, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Cook, Madge--Poems, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Council on Foreign Relations--Lamont, Thomas W., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Council on Foreign Relations--Resignation of Henry M. Wrist as President, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Council on Foreign Relations--Resolution Adopted by the Board of Directors, 1946 May 21 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Cousins, Norman--Wanted: Ten Billion Angry Men, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Dodd, Thomas J.--If Coexistence Fails (from Orbis), 1960 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Duggan, Laurence--In Memoriam, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Dunne, George--God Bless America, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Dwiggins, W.A--four-page Signature from Robert Nathan's One More Spring,1935 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - The Economist--"Containment Plus," 1952 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Edman, Irwin--If Not, Not, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D.--Guildhall Address in London and the Address Before the Congress in Washington, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D.--The Spirit of Geneva, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D.--A Tribute to Winston Spencer Churchill, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Emmett, Burton--"Notes for a Statement Regarding the Collection," P.M. Magazine Insert, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - The English-Speaking Union of the United States, 1958, 1965, (3 Folders) (Box 4, Folder 8 to 10)
    - Etheridge, Mark F.--"Of Whom Shall I Be Afraid?" 1953 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - France, Anatole--L'Affaire Crainquebille, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Fulbright, James William--"The Price of Empire," 1967 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Fulbright, James William--"Toward a More Creative Foreign Policy," 1959 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Calantiere, Lewis--"America Today," 1950 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Galbraith, John Kenneth--"How Keynes Came to America," 1965 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - George VI, King of Great Britain Donors to the King George VI Memorial Fund, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Gist, Thomas--Indian Captivity, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Coldenson, Samuel--Philip J. Goodhart, 1856-1944, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Greenman, Frederick F.--Wire Tapping and Civil Liberties, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - "Alfred Whitney Griswald: In Memoriam," 1964 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Griswold, Alfred Whitney--Inaugural Address, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Grolier Club--Report of the House Committee, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Haight, Anne Lyon--"Charles Dickens Tries to Remain Anonymous" and "Notes on the Loving Ballad of Lord Bateman," 1939 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Haight, Anne Lyon--Morals, Manners, Etiquette and the Three R's, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Halifax, Lord Marquess of, George Saville--"The Lady's New Year's Gift," 1935 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Hand, Learned--"Liberty," 1941 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Hand, Learned--"Rational Inquiry and the Triumph of Wisdom," 1954 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Heilbronner, Robert L.--"New Horizons in Economics," 1964 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - High, Stanley--"To Chick - At Fifty," 1952 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Horsfall, Percy--"Thanksgiving for the Life and Work of Robert Henry Brand," 1963 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Hubby, Germain A.--Commemoration of New Canaan Country School, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Jackson, Barbara Ward--"Herbert Lehman at 80," 1958 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Jacobs, Walter and Alain White--Variation Play: A Study in the Mechnisms and Relationship of Black Moves in the Two-Move Chess Problem, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Johnson, Lyndon Baines--"An Eloquent Plea-for Action: An Address Delivered Before a Joint Session of Congress," 1963 November 27 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Judah Magnes Foundation--Judah Magnes Memorial Booklet, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Kennan, George--"The Liberal Arts in Contemporary American Society," 1953 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Kennedy, John F.--An Address Delivered Before the Massachusetts Legislature, January 9, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Kerr, Jean--"Toujour Tristess," 1957 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - King, Martin Luther Jr.--"Letters From Birminghton Jail," 1968 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Lane, Margaret--L'Amitie Amoureuse, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Lasalle, Ferdinand--Une Page d'Amour de Ferdinand Lasalle, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Lehman, Irving--"Benjamin Nathan Cardozo," 1938 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - "Sam A. Lewisohn, 1884-1951," 1951 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Leyburn, James G.--Pierson College: The First Decade, 1933-1943. 1944 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Lippman, Walter--The Confrontation, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Luce, Clare Boothe--"Little Rock and the Muscovite Moon: Challenges to American Leadership, An Address," 1957 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - MacArthur, Douglas--An Address Delivered at Los Angeles, California, 1955 January 26 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - McLeish, Archibald--"The Great American Frustration," 1968 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Malgaigne, Joseph Francois--Conseils pour le Choix dune Bibliotheque Ecrits pour une Jeune Fille, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Malik, Charles--"The Problem of Asia," 1951 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Malik, Charles--War and Peace, 1950 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Mallory, Walter H.--Remarks at a Small Dinner on the Occasion of his Retirement as Exective Director of the Council on Foreign Relations, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Mansfield, Comins--"Adventures in Composition," 1944 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Maude, Angus--"Why is Waffle?" 1957 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - May, George O.--"Truth and Usefulness in Accounting," 1950 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Meredith, George--"Modern Love," 1942 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Merrick, Leonard--Conrad in Quest of His Youth, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Meyer, Agnes--"Freedom of the Mind," 1953 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Meyer, Ernest L.--"A Footnote on L'Amour," 1947 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Mill, John Stuart--"On Liberty," 1964 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Muggeridge, Malcolm--"Senator McCarthy McCartyized: Or, The Biter Bit," 1953 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Nathan, Robert and W.A. Dwiggins (Illustrator)--"One More Spring," 1935 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Nevinson, Henry W.--Farewell to America, 1935 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - New York Court of Appeals--"In Memoriam: Irving Lehman, 1876 - 1945," 1945 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - New York Supreme Court Anniversary, 1941 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - New Yorker Magazine--"The Night of the Blackout," 1965 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Nixon, Richard M., John Kennedy--"On the Results of the Election, 1960"(cover title: "A Gleam of Light Ahead") Foreword by Frank and Helen Altschul, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Paix et Liberte, Paris--"Balance Sheet of a Dictatorship," undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Perry, Ralph Barton and Rudolph Ruzicka (Illustrator)--"Plea for an Age Movement," 1943 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Phillips, Wendell--Toussaint L'Ouverture, 1963 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Pinckney, Mary Stead--Letter Book: November 14th, 1796 to August 29th, 1794, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Plimpton, Francis T.P.--"In Praise of Polygamy," 1957 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Prevost, Abbe and T.M. Cleland--"Histoire du Chevalier des Grieux et de Manon Lescaut," 1958 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Project Hope Journal, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Ransom, Will--"A Brochure in Honor of Gutenberg," 1941 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Redfield, Robert--"Talk with a Stranger," 1958 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Reston, James B.--Eulogy for Orvil E. Dreyfoos, 1963 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - "James Harvey Rogers: In Memoriam," 1940 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - "The Round Table War Pamphlet: The Issue," 1940 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Schlesinger, Arthur M., Jr.--"Herbert H. Lehman: The Conservative as Radical," 1967 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Shepardson, Whitney H.--"Early History of the Council on Foreign Relations," 1960 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Steinbeck, John--A Letter Written in Reply to a Request for a Statement about His Ancestry, 1940 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Sterne, Laurence--A Sentimental Journey through France and Italy by Mr. Yorick, 1936 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Stevenson, Adlai E.--"Must We Have War?" 1954 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Stevenson, Robert Louis and Jean Hugo (Illustrator)--An Inland Voyage, 1938. Hugo, Jean, illustrator, (2 Folders) (Box 8, Folder 13 to 14)
    - Streeter, Edward--"Words of Welcome," 1962 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Thompson, Dorothy--The Abbey, the Museum, the Commons. 1941 and "In Support of the Precident," 1945 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Tompkins, Boylston A.--A Toast proposed by Boylston A. Tompkins on the Eve of the Wedding of Judith Lee Tompkins and Henry Taylor Compton, Jr., 1955 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - U.S. Congress, "Adverse Report of the Committee of the Judiciary," 1937 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Valentine, Alan--"A Modest Proposal for the Care and Use of Subversives," 1954 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Vandenberg, Arthur--"The American Position," 1948 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Van Tassel, Etta May--"Beyond Geography: A Few Poems," 1946 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Warren, Earl--"The Blessings of Liberty," 1955 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Wasson, R. Gordon--"Toward a Russian Policy," 1951 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Weizmann, Chaim--"Before the United Nations," 1947 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Welles, Sumner--An Address (not printed), 1943 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Wharton, Edith--Ethan Frome, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - White, Alain
      - Chess books, 1941 - 1949 (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - F. Gamage: An Artist in Chess Problems, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - F. Gamage--Second Book (not printed), 1943-1949 (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - White, Alain and Comins Mansfield--Frederick Gamage and Vincent Eaton: A Century of Two-Movers, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Wilde, Oscar and Rudolph Ruzicka--The Happy Prince and Other Tales, 1936 (Box 9)
    - Willkie, Wendell Lewis--Occasional Addresses, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Wilson, Woodrow--"Leaders of Men," 1950-1951 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Wilson, Woodrow--"The Road Away from Revolution," 1948 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Wolfers, Arnold--"Eulogy for William M. Burden III," 1962 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - The Woodrow Wilson Foundation--Joseph Daniels Memorial Tribute, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Yale University--Report of the President's Advisory Committee, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Zenger, John Peter--"A Brief Narrative of the Trial of John Peter Zenger," 1947 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Zilborg, Gregory--"I Won't Apologize: Two Letters," 1939 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Subseries I.3: General Correspondence, 1934-1978
    This subseries is comprised of general correspondence arranged by year. It includes requests for books and pamphlets, correspondence with other presses, and the occasional letter of praise from an enthusiastic collector. In most cases, both the incoming mail and copies of Overbrook's responses are present.
    - General, 1934-1940 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - General, 1960-1965, (4 Folders) (Box 9, Folder 11 to 14)
    - General, 1966-1978, (4 Folders) (Box 11, Folder 1 to 4)
- Series II: General, 1929-1977
  This small but varied series contains documents related to the operation of the press, including financial records, internal correspondence, and paper samples. It also holds copies of the Overbrook Bibliography and information on book exhibits.
  - The American Institute of Graphic Arts. Fifty Books of the Year Exhibitions, 1939, 1942, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Andrade, Barry Jack de Costa--Chess Problems, 1944-1948 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Bibliographies of Overbrook Press from 1934-1969 by Norman Strouse, 1973-1975 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - University of California--Exhibition of Overbrook Press Books, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Census and Federal Trade Commission--U.S. Correspondence, 1943-1944 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - The Columbiad Club--Hartford Book Show, 1938 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Electoral Charts, 1936 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Employment--Illustrators and Artists, 1939 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Evans Margaret B., Art Director--Memos, 1940 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Financial, 1929-1937, (3 Folders) (Box 12, Folder 8 to 10)
  - Financial, 1938-1947 (Box 13, Folder 1 to 3)
  - Financial--Stamford Trust Company, 1944-1949 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Inquiries and Requests, 1935-1961 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Inventories, Orders and Recipients of Books, 1936-1977 (Box 14, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Legal Discussions--Memos and Minutes, 1933-1944 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - New York Times National Book Fair, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Orders, 1956-1965 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Paper samples and type specimens, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Sloan, Frank R., 1946-1947 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Strouse, Norman--"The Overbrook Press: An Example of Collecting in Depth," 1975 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Printed Items, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Inventory, 1967-1977 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Legal Documents, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 12)